Here we go!
Abe-chan!
Yes!
Puff puff!
That's right, today we're going to have
As you can see
I'm visiting
at Waraki Robot's training facility!
Yay!
Please take care of them!
I'm visiting you.
I'm so happy to see you.
Thank you very much.
That's why you're always like that.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
It's not a small, cozy place.
Yes, it is.
Your voice is clear.
Oh!
It's echoing.
It's so resonant, it's like...
You're not listening.
Huh!
Is that what you're saying?
That's impossible.
This place is huge.
But what do you see?
I mean...
Yes, I do.
We see...
We're here for the Herbtime show.
In the herb time show
We're going to perform.
Yes!
Thank you very much!
First of all, we're here at Waraki.
Thank you very much! Thank you!
Thank you so much!
We love you guys!
In our herbal time show.
Maybe we'll have a ball
I'm trying to decide.
There was a scene
At the dance-in.
And the last one after that.
For the last part.
Rehearse it.
Okay.
Um...
We were all wiped out.
Everyone was terrible.
Everyone's just...
No, it's really bad.
It's like they're shooting at us.
I mean, there's staging, but...
But if we don't get one in...
It's a little embarrassing.
That's right.
I'm going to put on a show.
I know.
It's the last song.
I want to make the audience go, "Oh!
I want to play it at least once.
I want to make a decision.
If we're going to go all the way...
I'm not sure about this one.
I'm going to practice today.
I'm going to practice today!
Wow!
Thank you!
I'll do it.
You know what? You know what?
Like My Draper
My Pretty Fortune
I don't want to be in a chain
I want to make it happen with you
Another Mind
Tell me now
There's no meaning
If it's a word, I don't need it anymore
It's up now
You and me so
If you're gonna practice
I'll do it right
It's up to you and me so
If you put it on nicely.
Shape.
You shouldn't say anything about my voice.
Why not?
Um...
Rehearsal footage.
Rehearsal footage of Suzuki.
Look at his feet.
His feet.
His form...
I mean...
I should do it myself.
I'd probably get in better.
I'm...
I'm a numbers guy.
No!
If you're going to do it, do it right.
You're the oldest, and now you're in.
I'm serious.
You should see the big one.
Did you do it?
If you're going to do it, do it right.
Mr. Suzuki was the worst. Mr. Suzuki was the worst.
But you want to learn.
That's for sure.
And if you can do it...
It would be cool.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
Alves.
Why?
No, it's not.
Hey, guys, check this out.
Right this way.
What is it?
A book.
It's a book.
This is really...
A world-famous
A basketball cartoon.
Please read it.
Yes, sir.
Here you go.
Back of the ball.
Legorday.
Huh?
Slam dancer.
I've heard of this place.
Have you seen it?
No.
When you give up...
The game is over.
That's what I'm saying.
If you give up, the game is over.
May I read this?
Same level here.
Ah!
But there's a very famous slam dunk
It's right here.
Look at this slam dunk. Watch this slam dunk.
I mean, let's study it.
That's what I'm talking about.
He can hit 20,000 balls.
Hanamichi?
I think it's amazing how hard Hanamichi works.
When I saw this...
I thought so!
That's right.
I'm going to watch this while I study.
Let's hit 20,000 balls.
I know it's not a textbook, but...
We probably only have an hour or so.
The doctor's conference is over.
20,000 balls each.
You learn everything you can from the world.
We start with the basics.
You haven't read it.
The basics, the fundamentals.
You're the main character.
That's it, isn't it?
Hey, Mr. White.
The teacher's here!
He's talking about basic fundamentals.
But if you don't know what you're capable of...
I can't start anything.
So, for now, we'll each take 10 shots.
Let's see what kind of form you're in and what kind of ability you have.
and what kind of form you have, and what kind of ability you have.
Yes, that's right.
Let's start with you, Airi.
Okay.
I'll give it a try.
We'll assist.
Ten.
When you're done, you're in the center. center if necessary
Yes, sir.
Yes Yes
Second time
Yes, sir.
This is bad, isn't it?
Second one.
I'm okay now.
Yes, sir.
That was close.
We did it.
Ten.
Yes, sir.
Wow.
Start.
Yes, sir.
Eight.
Nine.
Start
Sto rt
16 16
Fast Forward】 【Fast Forward
Fast forward】 【Fast forward】 【Fast forward】 【Fast forward
Fast forward】 【Fast forward】 【Fast forward】 【Fast forward】 【Fast forward
Fast forward】 【Fast forward】 【Fast forward】 【Fast forward】 【Fast forward】 【Fast forward
[fast forward] [fast forward] [fast forward] [fast forward] [fast forward] [fast forward]
[fast forward] [fast forward] [fast forward] [fast forward] [fast forward] [fast forward
Uh-oh.
lasciose
lie
End
Okay, so everyone is done throwing, but
Once again, Aina Once again, Ai Naga
also a yuga
Yuzu also 1
Hana is 2
Oh my God!
It's devastating!
It's terrible!
It's not good.
But then again, they weren't all that good.
They're all like a few acorns too big.
He said the smallest one was fine.
So who's on the right?
I'd say Hirayuru.
Matsukiku...
That's terrible!
The basics are important!
It's like he's sending it rather than throwing it.
He's flapping his wings 10 times!
Basics are important!
It's important, isn't it?
Did you feel it in your body?
Yes, I did.
Just like Yuka said.
Experience Award
I did the mini-mass.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Let's read it once.
Let's read it one more time.
Let's read it again!
Maybe if Hanamichi taught me something, it might be different.
It might be like that.
Let's read it one more time and compare.
Hanamichi, too...
It's the same.
Can't you go?
I'm sure. I'm telling the truth.
Puller?
I'll get the puller.
I can feel it.
Yeah.